http://www.galferusa.com/shop/policies

About GalferUSA
Why choose Galfer?
ONLINE SHIPPING POLICY
Saturday-Monday online store orders are not processed until the following Tuesday. Please allow production time for Brake Line kits that are not in stock or built to order at our US facility in Southern, CA. Expect 2-4 business days for production of colored lines, (black, blue, red and gold) fittings/bolts and ABS Brake Line kits are built to order. Custom line production also has a 2-4 business days turn around. Shipping only on business days (Tuesday-Friday) as Galfer USA is closed weekends and Monday's. Expedited shipping option does NOT expedite the order, only applies for shipping. "RUSH" charge option (Expedited Manufacturing) is available or for assistance please contact Sales at Sales@GalferUSA.com (805) 988-2900 Ext: 109
ONLINE PAYMENT POLICY
International orders must be paid by Pay-Pal, Card payments will NOT be accpeted. Option for Pay-Pal will be offered at checkout. Thank you for your understanding. Further questions please contact Sales at Sales@GalferUSA.com
RETURN POLICY
Products can only be returned if they were purchased directly from Galfer USA. If purchased through a third party, they must be returned to the retailer for credit or exchange. If you are in need of warranty assistance, please refer to the policies below and feel free to contact us directly. Galfer USA does not accept returns on custom lines, nor lines that have had their length or colors altered from standard specifications. All return shipments must be clearly marked with a valid Return Authorization Number (RA#) or they will be refused by our Receiving Department. All returns are subject to a 15% restocking fee. For more information, or to be issued a RA#, please contact our Customer Service Department at CustomerService@GalferUSA.com or (805) 988-2900 Ext: 112
WARRANTY POLICY
-BRAKE LINES
All Galfer USA brake lines are covered by our limited lifetime warranty to the original purchaser. As this encompasses a large number of possible scenarios, please contact our Customer Service Department at CustomerService@GalferUSA.com or (805) 988-2900 Ext: 112 for details.
-BRAKE ROTORS
All Galfer USA brake rotors are covered by a 6 month warranty from the original purchase date. We require the exclusive use of Galfer brake pads to retain this warranty. If outside the warranty period, rotors can be sent in for free inspection. The customer is responsible for shipping charges to and from our location in Carson City, NV. Please make sure to contact us for a Return Authorization number before sending in your rotors. For more information, or to be issued a RA#, please contact our Customer Service Department at CustomerService@GalferUSA.com or (805) 988-2900 Ext: 112
-BRAKE PADS
Galfer USA does not have a specific warranty period for brake pads as they are considered consumable items. However, if you are dissatisfied with your Galfer brake pads for any reason, please contact our Customer Service Department at CustomerService@GalferUSA.com or (805) 988-2900 Ext: 112, and we will address your concerns on a case-by-case basis.
CALIFORNIA PROPOSITION 65
For more information on California Prop. 65, click here.
PRIVACY NOTICE
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for GalferUSA.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
SECURITY
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a lock icon in the address bar and looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the Web page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at 805-988-2900.
TRADEMARK
WAVE® is a trademark of Galfer USA. Tsunami™ is a trademark of Galfer USA. Any entities other than Galfer USA authorized dealers do not retain the right to use either WaveÂ® or Tsunami™. Any brake disc using the name Wave® or Tsunami™ and is not manufactured by Galfer USA is not a true Wave®.
Part Search
Products
Brake Kits
Brake Rotors
Brake Pads
Lines
Custom Line Builder
Accossato
Why choose Galfer?
